<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>Automated Message for Transcript Creation</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>PIC - Send Transcript To Customer</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>{!LiveChatTranscript.Subject__c}</subject>
    <textOnly>Thank you for your interest in TE Connectivity.

You have recently contacted our technical support department using our Live Chat option. Enclosed in this email is a transcript of your chat session.


Transcript Reference Number: {!LiveChatTranscript.Name}

Transcript:

{!LiveChatTranscript.Body}

{!Case.Thread_Id}

How can we provide an extraordinary Customer Experience?
Let Us Know

English: Users of TE products should make their own evaluation of the information / data provided to determine the suitability of each such product for the specific application. The information given herein, including cross-reference part numbers, drawings, illustrations and schematics which are intended for information or illustration purposes only, is believed to be reliable. However, TE Connectivity makes no warranties as to its accuracy or completeness and disclaims any liability in connections with its use. TE Connectivity&apos;s obligations shall only be as set forth in TE Connectivity&apos;s Standard Terms and Conditions of Sale for this product and in no case will TE Connectivity be liable for any incidental, indirect or consequential damages arising out of the sale, resale, use or misuse of the product. Users of TE Connectivity products should make their own evaluation to determine the suitability of each such product for the specific application.

Mandarin: 免责条款：对于我们所提供的产品信息或数据资料，客户需要根据自己的应用评估是否符合其特定的使用需求。这些信息包括竞争对手替代料号，图纸，图表数据等，都只供客户参考，尽管这些数据和信息都是真实可靠的，但我们不保证和客户的应用一定完全精确匹配。我们的义务和责任符合标准产品销售条款条例的规定，我们拒绝对任何由销售，转售，使用或者使用不当而导致的附随损失或间接损失承担赔偿责任。客户需要自行决定所提供的信息是否适合其需求和应用

© 2016 TE Connectivity Ltd. family of companies. All Rights Reserved.
TE Connectivity, and TE Logo are trademarks. Other company, product and service names
may be trademarks or service marks of others. References in this e-mail to TE
Connectivity products or services do not imply that Tyco Electronics Corporation intends
to make them available in all countries.

Copyright Statement | Privacy Policy

Tyco Electronics Corporation
1050 Westlakes Drive, Berwyn, PA, 19312</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
